Neil Dixon-Crawford

707-1 Grosvenor St. London ON N6A 1Y3 neilpdixon@gmail.com | neilpdixon.me | 519.854.5891

Summary of Qualifications

Project Execution Skills: Has completed numerous design project working with teams

both at school and at work

Relevant Job Skills: Experience working with adobe software such as illustrator,

Photoshop and After Effects.

Communications Skills: Outstanding verbal and written skills, strives at public

speaking.

Academic Qualifications

Sept 2013 - present Candidate for Bachelor of Global Business

And Digital Arts, University of Waterloo

Waterloo, Ontario

Work Experience

June 2014 – present Ministry of Child and Youth Services – Project and

Communications Assistant

Assisting in digital design projects, updating presentations and

webinars in databases and A/V support

Aug 2015 – present Residence Life Don

Responsible for ensuring the safety and well being of 40 students Plan weekly floor events for educational and community purposes

Apr 2011- Jan 2014 Real Canadian Superstore - Front End Cashier

Working well under pressure

Responsible for all transactions and operation of registers

Dec 2010-Apr 2011 Real Canadian Superstore - Electronics Department

Assist customers with inquiries and purchases

Processed customer transactions

Worked as part of a team.

Volunteer/Leadership Experience

University of Waterloo Stratford Campus Ambassador

January 2014 – present

Interacting with students at University open houses, march break events and conferences

University of Waterloo English Conversation Partner

January 2014 – April 2014

Held meetings with international students to help improve their English proficiency.

University of Waterloo Arts Peer Mentor

September 2014 - present

Hosting office hours once a week and answering any questions students have regarding their program in the arts faculty.

The Make-A-Wish Foundation of Canada

February 2013- April 2013

Lead Organizer of a Charity Fashion Show "STRUT" to raise funds to send a young girl and her family to Disney World. This show raised \$3000.

Completed Projects

Jan 2015 - Apr 2015 Ch!p In Application: GBDA 228 - Digital Imaging

Designed a prototype for a volunteer mobile app that would efficiently connect volunteers with volunteering positions Successfully collaborated in a group dynamic.

Sept 2014 – Dec 2014 Square Eyes Documentary

Produced an informative video about screen addiction Set up and organized a production schedule Filmed and edited audio for film.

Awards/Scholarships

University of Waterloo Merit Scholarship – University of Waterloo

Qualifications & Activities

Certified CPR A and First Aid Training.

Participated in an intramural volleyball league every term of university.

Enjoys watching documentaries on a variety of topics.

Loves capturing moments in life via video and photography.